<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
        xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1"
        xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>1.0</priority>
        <content>The website of Katerina Tartary, a qualified sex therapist and psychologist. She provides support to individuals and couples, including those in polyamorous relationships and members of the LGBTQ+ community. Katerina employs Acceptance and Commitment Therapy (ACT) and Emotionally Focused Therapy (EFT). She offers a free initial consultation and conducts sessions in English, Russian, and French</content>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="en" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="ru" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="fr" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="canonical" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#about</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.9</priority>
        <content>Katerina Tartary is a sex therapist and consultant specializing in ACT and EFT, with a focus on assisting clients dealing with trauma from violence. Since 2022, she has been providing consultations to clients from 15 countries, organizing therapeutic retreats and art therapy for groups. She works with individuals of various gender identities and relationship structures, including polyamorous unions, helping them to recognize their values and build close relationships.</content>

        <video:video>
            <video:content_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/video/kate_en.mp4</video:content_loc>
            <video:thumbnail_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/images/poster.png</video:thumbnail_loc>
            <video:title>Welcome Video from Sex Therapist Katerina Tartary</video:title>
            <video:description>Katerina Tartary discusses the challenges people face in intimacy and her mission to help clients create harmonious and trusting relationships. She invites you to a free introductory session.</video:description>
            <video:duration>73</video:duration>
        </video:video>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#expertise</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Katerina Tartary works with clients on issues related to sexuality and relationships, including sexual dysfunctions, avoidance of emotional intimacy, communication difficulties, and crises. She helps address the consequences of sexualized violence, low self-esteem, uncontrolled emotions, and interpersonal conflicts.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#clients</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Katerina Tartary provides support to individual adults, couples (including monogamous and non-monogamous unions), families, and groups (friends and colleagues).</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#methods</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Katerina Tartary's methods include sex therapy, ACT (Acceptance and Commitment Therapy), EFT (Emotionally Focused Therapy), IFS for trauma and abuse work, and art therapy. These methods help address issues of intimacy, manage emotions, restore connections, and express feelings through creativity.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#benefits</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Reasons to choose Katerina Tartary: a scientific approach to therapy, feminist perspective, support for LGBTQIA+ and non-monogamous relationships, work with the consequences of violence, awareness of neurodiversity, continuous professional development, and multicultural experience. Consultations are available in English, French, and Russian.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#feedback</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Client testimonials for Katerina Tartary. Clients share their experiences of working with Katerina, describing how the sessions have helped them gain confidence, understand themselves better, and improve their relationships. Testimonials come from clients in various countries, including Russia, France, Belarus, Kazakhstan, and Georgia.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#steps</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Steps to work with Katerina Tartary. Clients can choose a convenient time for their first free session, receive confirmation with a Google Meet link and informed consent document, participate in the first session, and plan subsequent sessions as needed. Payment is to be made at least 24 hours before each session.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#price</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Pricing for consultations with Katerina Tartary. The first session is free, lasting 30 minutes for an introduction and to determine areas of focus. Individual sessions lasting 50 minutes cost €100, while couple or group sessions lasting 70 minutes start at €180.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#registration</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.9</priority>
        <content>Form to register for a free 30-minute introductory online session with Katerina Tartary. You can choose a convenient date and time and ask a question.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#faq</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Answers to frequently asked questions about sex therapy, explaining its principles, therapist education, session frequency and number, as well as confidentiality. Details about payment conditions and rescheduling sessions are described, along with recommendations for choosing individual or joint consultations.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#questions</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Form for anonymous questions about sexuality and relationships, allowing visitors to submit their questions without fear of judgment. Answers to some of the questions will be published in the therapist's Instagram blog, promoting openness and support.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/#contacts</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Subscription form for news. Visitors can leave their email addresses to receive updates and information from the therapist.</content>
    </url>

    <!-- Russian version -->

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.9</priority>
        <content>Сайт Катерины Тартари, квалифицированного секс-терапевта и психолога. Она оказывает поддержку индивидуально и парам, в том числе тем, кто состоит в полиаморных отношениях, представителям сообщества ЛГБТК+. Катерина использует терапию принятия и приверженности (ACT) и эмоционально-ориентированную терапию (EFT). Она предлагает бесплатную первичную консультацию и проводит сессии на английском, русском и французском языках.</content>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="en" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="ru" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="fr" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html"/>
        <xhtml:link rel="canonical" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
    </url>

     <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#about</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Катерина Тартари — секс-терапевтка и консультантка по ACT и EFT, специализирующаяся на помощи при травмах насилия. С 2022 года предоставляет консультации клиентам из 15 стран, организует терапевтические ретриты и арт-терапию для групп. Работает с людьми различных гендерных идентичностей и отношений, включая полиаморные союзы, помогает осознавать ценности и строить близкие отношения.</content>

        <video:video>
            <video:content_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/video/kate_ru_sub.mp4</video:content_loc>
            <video:thumbnail_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/images/poster.png</video:thumbnail_loc>
            <video:title>Приветственное видео от секс-терапевта Катерины Тартари</video:title>
            <video:description>Катерина Тартари рассказывает о сложностях, с которыми сталкиваются люди в сфере интимной близости, и о своей миссии — помочь клиентам создавать гармоничные и доверительные отношения. Приглашает на бесплатную ознакомительную сессию.</video:description>
            <video:duration>73</video:duration>
        </video:video>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#expertise</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Катерина Тартари работает с клиентами по вопросам сексуальности и отношений, включая сексуальные дисфункции, избегание эмоциональной близости, трудности в общении и кризисы. Помогает разобраться с последствиями сексуализированного насилия, низкой самооценкой, неуправляемыми эмоциями и межличностными конфликтами. </content>
    </url>

     <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#clients</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Катерина Тартари предоставляет поддержку индивидуально взрослым людям, парам (включая моногамные и немоногамные союзы), семьям и группам (друзья и коллеги).</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#methods</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Методы работы Катерины Тартари: секс-терапия, ACT (терапия принятия и ответственности), EFT (эмоционально фокусированная терапия), IFS для работы с травмами и абьюзом, а также арт-терапия. Эти методы помогают решать вопросы интимности, управлять эмоциями, восстанавливать связи и выражать чувства через творчество.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#benefits</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Почему выбирают Катерину Тартари: научный подход в терапии, феминистская оптика, поддержка ЛГБТКИА+ и немоногамных отношений, работа с последствиями насилия, информированность о нейроотличиях, постоянное повышение квалификации и мультикультурный опыт. Консультации на английском, французском и русском языках.</content>
    </url>

 <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#feedback</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Отзывы клиентов Катерины Тартари. Клиенты делятся своим опытом работы с Катериной, описывая, как сессии помогли им обрести уверенность, разобраться в себе, и наладить отношения. Отзывы от клиентов из разных стран, включая Россию, Францию, Беларусь, Казахстан и Грузию.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#steps</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Этапы работы с Катериной Тартари. Клиенты могут выбрать удобное время для первой бесплатной сессии, получают подтверждение с Google Meet ссылкой и документом об информированном согласии, участвуют в первой сессии и планируют последующие по мере необходимости. Оплата проводится минимум за 24 часа до каждой сессии.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#price</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.8</priority>
        <content>Стоимость консультаций с Катериной Тартари. Первая сессия — бесплатная, длительностью 30 минут для знакомства и определения направлений работы. Индивидуальные сессии длительностью 50 минут стоят 100 €, а парные или групповые сессии длительностью 70 минут — от 180 €.</content>
    </url>

     <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#registration</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.9</priority>
        <content>Форма записи на бесплатную 30-минутную ознакомительную онлайн-сессию с Катериной Тартари. Можно выбрать удобные дату и время, задать вопрос.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#faq</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Ответы на часто задаваемые вопросы о секс-терапии, объяснение ее принципов, образование терапевта, частота и количество сессий, а также конфиденциальность. Описаны условия оплаты и переносов сессий, рекомендации по выбору индивидуальных или совместных консультаций.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#questions</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Форма для анонимных вопросов о сексуальности и отношениях, позволяющая посетителям отправлять свои вопросы без страха осуждения. Ответы на некоторые из вопросов будут опубликованы в Instagram-блоге терапевта, способствуя открытости и поддержке.</content>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html#contacts</loc>
        <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
        <priority>0.7</priority>
        <content>Форма подписки на новости. Посетители могут оставлять адреса электронной почты для получения обновлений и информации от терапевта.</content>
    </url>

    <!-- Version française -->

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.9</priority>
    <content>Le site de Katerina Tartary, sexothérapeute qualifiée et psychologue. Elle offre un soutien aux individus et aux couples, y compris ceux en relations polyamoureuses et aux membres de la communauté LGBTQIA+. Katerina utilise la thérapie d'acceptation et d'engagement (ACT) et la thérapie centrée sur les émotions (EFT). Elle propose une consultation initiale gratuite et mène des séances en anglais, russe et français.</content>
    <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="en" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
    <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="ru" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/ru.html"/>
    <xhtml:link rel="alternate" hreflang="fr" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html"/>
    <xhtml:link rel="canonical" href="https://katerina-tartary.com/"/>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#about</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Katerina Tartary est sexothérapeute et consultante en ACT et EFT, spécialisée dans l'aide aux traumatismes liés à la violence. Depuis 2022, elle consulte des clients de 15 pays, organise des retraites thérapeutiques et des séances d'art-thérapie pour des groupes. Elle travaille avec des personnes de diverses identités de genre et types de relations, y compris des unions polyamoureuses, en aidant à prendre conscience des valeurs et à établir des relations intimes.</content>

    <video:video>
        <video:content_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/video/kate_fr.mp4</video:content_loc>
        <video:thumbnail_loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/assets/images/poster.png</video:thumbnail_loc>
        <video:title>Vidéo de bienvenue de la sexothérapeute Katerina Tartary</video:title>
        <video:description>Katerina Tartary parle des difficultés rencontrées par les gens dans le domaine de l'intimité et de sa mission d'aider les clients à créer des relations harmonieuses et de confiance. Elle invite à une séance d'initiation gratuite.</video:description>
        <video:duration>73</video:duration>
    </video:video>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#expertise</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Katerina Tartary travaille avec des clients sur des questions de sexualité et de relations, y compris les dysfonctions sexuelles, l'évitement de l'intimité émotionnelle, les difficultés de communication et les crises. Elle aide à gérer les conséquences de la violence sexualisée, une faible estime de soi, des émotions incontrôlables et des conflits interpersonnels.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#clients</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Katerina Tartary fournit un soutien aux adultes individuellement, aux couples (y compris les unions monogames et non monogames), aux familles et aux groupes (amis et collègues).</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#methods</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Les méthodes de Katerina Tartary comprennent la sexothérapie, l'ACT (thérapie d'acceptation et d'engagement), l'EFT (thérapie émotionnelle focalisée), l'IFS pour travailler sur les traumatismes et les abus, ainsi que l'art-thérapie. Ces méthodes aident à aborder les questions d'intimité, à gérer les émotions, à rétablir des liens et à exprimer des sentiments par la créativité.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#benefits</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Pourquoi choisir Katerina Tartary : approche scientifique en thérapie, perspective féministe, soutien aux relations LGBTQIA+ et non monogames, travail sur les conséquences de la violence, sensibilisation aux neurodifférences, formation continue et expérience multiculturelle. Consultations en anglais, français et russe.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#feedback</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Avis des clients de Katerina Tartary. Les clients partagent leur expérience de travail avec Katerina, décrivant comment les séances les ont aidés à gagner en confiance, à se comprendre et à améliorer leurs relations. Témoignages de clients de différents pays, y compris la Russie, la France, la Biélorussie, le Kazakhstan et la Géorgie.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#steps</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Les étapes de travail avec Katerina Tartary. Les clients peuvent choisir un moment qui leur convient pour leur première séance gratuite, recevoir une confirmation avec un lien Google Meet et un document de consentement éclairé, participer à la première séance et planifier les suivantes au besoin. Le paiement est effectué au moins 24 heures avant chaque séance.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#price</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.8</priority>
    <content>Tarifs des consultations avec Katerina Tartary. La première séance est gratuite, d'une durée de 30 minutes pour faire connaissance et déterminer les axes de travail. Les séances individuelles de 50 minutes coûtent 100 €, tandis que les séances de couple ou de groupe de 70 minutes commencent à 180 €.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#registration</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.9</priority>
    <content>Formulaire d'inscription pour une séance d'initiation en ligne de 30 minutes gratuite avec Katerina Tartary. Il est possible de choisir une date et une heure qui conviennent, et de poser une question.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#faq</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.7</priority>
    <content>Réponses aux questions fréquentes sur la sexothérapie, explication de ses principes, formation du thérapeute, fréquence et nombre de séances, ainsi que confidentialité. Conditions de paiement et de report des séances, recommandations pour choisir des consultations individuelles ou conjointes.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#questions</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.7</priority>
    <content>Formulaire pour des questions anonymes sur la sexualité et les relations, permettant aux visiteurs d'envoyer leurs questions sans crainte de jugement. Les réponses à certaines questions seront publiées dans le blog Instagram du thérapeute, favorisant l'ouverture et le soutien.</content>
</url>

<url>
    <loc>https://katerina-tartary.com/fr.html#contacts</loc>
    <lastmod>2024-10-31T17:07:37+01:00</lastmod>
    <priority>0.7</priority>
    <content>Formulaire d'inscription aux nouvelles. Les visiteurs peuvent laisser des adresses e-mail pour recevoir des mises à jour et des informations de la part du thérapeute.</content>
</url>

</urlset>